亚伯:嘿,男子出游日真是个好主意.
Abe: Hey, the seniors guys day out was one great idea.
本:对,只有我们四个,出来玩.
Ben: Yeah, it was four guys, out on the town.
迈克:想吃就吃…
Mike: Eating anything we want...
杰森:路过折扣珠宝店,不用再进去了…
Jason: Walking past discount jewelers without missing a beat...
本:嘿,你们还记得上个月吗?
Ben: Hey, you guys remember last month,
妈妈和开萝尔看斗牛比赛去了.
when mom and Carol came to that Bulls game?
迈克:哦,是的.
Mike: Oh yeah, remember what she said?
记得她说什么了吗?
It's just not fair because some of the guys were so much taller than the
这太不公平了,因为有些人的个比其他人高多了.
others.
杰森:不好…
Jason: Guys...
本和迈克:怎么了?
Ben and Mike: What?
杰森:出事了;我们的火车定点到了.
Jason: Something is wrong; our train is leaving on time.
巴尼:你们有谁想试试手气?一美元能挣两美元,
Barney: Any of you fellas care to chase your luck?A dollar will get you two.
杰森:不,谢谢…
Jason: No thank you...
巴尼:嘿,你们有什么急事要赶啊.
Barney: Hey all you got to do is find the queen.
亚伯:巴尼?
Abe: Barney?
巴尼:亚伯!!!
Barney: Abe!!!Hey man, I have been worried sick about you...
我担心死你了…你到哪里去了?
Where have you been?
亚伯:哦,我很好.我一直在郊区住着.
Abe: Oh I'm fine, I've been living with the family in the suburbs.
巴尼:哦,太好了…他们发现了吗?
Barney: Oh that's great...Have they found out yet?
杰森:对不起,我是杰森西沃.
Jason: Excuse me, I'm Jason Seaver.
巴尼:哦,巴尼帕帕达基斯…小子,你焕然一新.你失踪了!!
Barney: Oh, Barney Papadakis...Boy you clean up good.You're gone!!
亚伯:你看起来也不错,巴尼.
Abe: You look good too Barney'
巴尼:是的,这都靠了新的训练计划.
Barney: Yeah well, it's this new exercise program.
我一看见巡警撒腿就跑.
Every time I see a transit cop I run a quarter of a mile.
他叫什么来着…安德森先生…真喜欢你的装备!蓝色很适合你.
Speaking of which...Mr.Anderson...love the outfit!Blue is your color.
安德森先生:你不能在这里进行任何非法的赌博活动,明白吗?
Mr.Anderson: You wouldn't be running any illegal gambling here now would you?
巴尼:我没有.你看实际上,我在玩接龙游戏呢.
Barney: No, you see actually I was playing 52 card pick up.
安德森先生:用三张牌吗?
Mr.Anderson: With three cards?
巴尼:我还没学好.
Barney: I'm not very good.
安德森先生:走开,巴尼…
Mr.Anderson: Beat it Barney...
巴尼:好的…很久没见了,伙计.
Barney: Gotcha...Well so long fellows.
我要走很长一段路到汽车站看看.
I got enough quarters to go to the bus station to walk the whole mily dud.
很高兴见到你,亚伯.
Nice seeing ya Abe.
亚伯:再见,巴尼.
Abe: See ya Barney.
杰森:你认识这个人吗?
Jason: So, you know this guy hm?
亚伯:这条街上的人都认识巴尼.如果你想找个地方睡觉,
Abe: Everybody on this street knows Barney.
找点吃的,巴尼可以帮你.
If you need a place to sleep and some food, Barney is the guy to see.
杰森:如果他是个好人,搞点扑克小把戏也无伤大雅.
Jason: and if he's good, I guess he can do all right running a cards scam.
亚伯:那可不是小把戏.巴尼是纽约唯一的"三张牌"高手.
Abe: It's not a scam.Barney is New York's only 3 card Monty player.
他手上的动作比兔子跑的还快.
He's got faster hands than warren batty.
本:他为什么叫你亚伯?
Ben: Why does he call you Abe?
亚伯:哦,这是因为我跟林肯是同一天的生日.
Abe: Well, it's because my birthday's the same as Lincoln's.
迈克:你生日是12月25日吗?
Mike: Your birthday is December 25th?
杰森:2月12日.
Jason: February 12th.
亚伯:是的.
Abe: Right.
迈克:等等,下周就是你的生日?
Mike: Wait a minute.your birthday is next week?
你怎么不告诉我们呢?
And you didn't tell us about it?
本:你真傻?不说怎么能得到好礼物呢?
Ben: What are you nuts?How do you expect to get any good presents?
亚伯:嘿,我不需要什么礼物的.
Abe: Hey I don't need any presents.
本:哦,卢克…他在开玩笑呢,
Ben: Oh Luke....He's Just kidding now...
爸爸…实际上,他想要件皮夹克,尺寸和我一样的.
Actually he wants a leather jacket in my size.
亚伯:我不是跟你说过很多遍了吗?我不想你们为我开什么晚会.
Abe: How many times do I have to tell you?I don't want you guys throwing me a party.
迈克:卢克,我只是说弄一些土豆条和一个气球或两个…
Mike: Luke I'm just talking about some potato chips and a balloon or two...
克莉丝:我有个好主意!!
Chrissy: I have a great idea!!
迈克:什么主意?
Mike: What?
克莉丝:去小鸡奶酪店.
Chrissy: Go to Chucky cheese.
本:对,好.卢克真的想这么过生日吗,向6英尺高的机器老鼠身上扔意大利腊肠?
Ben: Yeah right.Luke really wants to spend his 16th birthday throwing pepperoni at six foot mechanical mice.
克莉丝:这才是晚会呢!
Chrissy: Now that's a party!
本:晚会好坏的秘诀就是看谁不参加.
Ben: The secret to a great party is who isn't there when you have it.
亚伯:哦?
Abe: Hu?
本:你知道,一个更亲密的聚会.
Ben: You know, a more private gathering.
亚伯:你是说只有你和我?
Abe: You mean just you and me?
麦琪:本想说的是你应该等到我和杰森出门以后再在家里举行一个疯狂的聚会.
Maggie: What Ben is trying to say is that you should wait until Jason
and I are out and have a wild party here in the house.
本:我们可以这么做的…
Ben: Or we could do that...
杰森:算了吧.
Jason: Forget it.
本:嘿,这是妈妈的主意.
Ben: Hey it was mom's idea.
亚伯:好,好,我放弃.随便你们怎么安排.
Abe: Ok,ok,ok, I give up.You can throw me a party.
迈克:好的!!!
Mike: All right!!!
亚伯:但求你们,不要太隆重,好吗?
Abe: But please, don't make it a big deal, all right?
迈克:怎么能大吗?妈妈和爸爸坚持参加.
Mike: How can we?Mom and dad insist on being there.
本:完了,晚会看来要泡汤了.不过,我们可以给你一大把的礼物.
Ben: Look, the party is going to be a dud.But we can still make
out like a bandit on the gifts
亚伯:我不想收什么礼物.
Abe: But I don't want any gifts.
本:你别老是想着你自己啊.
Ben: would you quit thinking of yourself?
麦琪:好了,克莉丝,
Maggie: Ok Chrissy, time for.....Chrissy.....
该睡…克莉丝…你又在玩我的首饰盒吗?我告诉过你不要这样.
were you playing in my jewelry box again after I told you not to?
克莉丝:你怎么知道的呢?
Chrissy: Why would you think that?
麦琪:因为你的喷气孔先生正戴着我的珍珠耳环呢.
Maggie: Because Mr.Blowhole is wearing my good pearl earrings.
克莉丝:坏鲸鱼!!坏鲸鱼!!!
Chrissy: Bad whale!!Bad whale!!!
迈克:我说,伙计们,我要把这次生日晚会搞成最好的.
Mike: You know guys, I'm going to make this the best birthday party ever.
我有个主意.这个主意太棒了,连我都佩服自己.
I've got an idea.This idea is so great, it even scares me.
杰森:上次你就是这么说的.可你让我失望了.
Jason: Last time he said that, I lost my eyebrows.
麦琪:嗨,德怀特.
Maggie: Hi Dwight.
德怀特:这是货车的钥匙.
Dwight: Here's the keys to the wagon.
麦琪:开萝尔的飞机安全起飞了吗?
Maggie: Did carol's plane get off safely?
德怀特:不幸,是的.
Dwight: Unfortunately yes.
千万别误会我…我很高兴她还活着,
Don't get me wrong...
但是她到大英博物馆去做研究,
I'm glad she's alive and all but what the heck am I going to do for
那我这一个月的时间该怎么过呢?
a month while she's away doing research at the British museum?
杰森:哦,别太看重这事,
Jason: Oh don't take it so hard Dwight,
德怀特.她转眼就会回来的.
she's going to be back before you know it.
你提醒了我,她的飞机6个小时前起飞的…你干什么去了?
Which reminds me, her plane left 6 hours ago...Where have you been?
德怀特:哦,我就站在那里,
Dwight: Well I stood there and I watched the vapor trail from her plane
望着她的飞机在空中留下的痕迹.
evaporate.
麦琪:看了6个小时?
Maggie: For 6 hour?
德怀特:不,只是5分钟.
Dwight: No, for five minutes.
然后,我做了任何美国热血青年都会做的事.
And then I did what any red blooded American man would do.
杰森:德怀特,你喝酒了吗?
Jason: Dwight have you been drinking?
德怀特:哦,如果不坦白,
Dwight: Well, I'd be a liar if I didn't confess.
我就成了骗子了.我信步走到布瑞克大街的电影院,花了些钱打发时间了.
I went down and I knocked back a few yuhus at the bleaker's street cinema.
麦琪:你去看电影了?
Maggie: You went to the movies?
德怀特:是先锋派电影节的获奖影片-
Dwight: And I saw the avant-garde film festival winner, death of an avocado.
杰森:让我猜猜,
Jason: Let me just guess here,
影片的结尾跟木匠有关吗?
but the ending had something to do with guacamole?
德怀特:我看到有把蓝色的草坪躺椅.有一个老人走过来,
Dwight: We see this blue lawn chair.
坐上去.
Then this old man comes, and he sits down on it and he plays the xylophone,
他手里弹着木琴,然后就死了.
and then he dies.
麦琪:就这些?
Maggie: That's it?
德怀特:它讲述的是人们反反复复寻求一种超自然安逸的情怀.
Dwight: It's a statement about mans tautological search for metaphysical comfort.
麦琪:那么梨树呢?
Maggie: Where's the avocado?
德怀特:没有梨树.哦,
Dwight: There is no avocado.
这有点太简单了,是不是?
Well, that would be a little bit obvious don't you think?
麦琪:我的小马驹,这是卢克让我们拿的横幅吗?
Maggie: My little pony?Is this the banner Luke wanted us to get?
克莉丝:这是卢克最喜欢的.
Chrissy: It's Luke's favorite.
麦琪:真的吗?
Maggie: Are you sure?
克莉丝:反正有人最喜欢.
Chrissy: It's someone's favorite.
杰森:嘿…真不懂人们为什么不到摩茨晚会仓库看一看?
Jason: Hey...you know I don't know why more people don't shop down at
那儿的好东西可不少…瞧这个,
Morts party warehouse.They have some great deals down there...Look at this.
麦琪:这也是好东西?
Maggie: What's that supposed to be?
杰森:这只是赠品而已.我买了20顶晚会帽子,
Jason: It's pin the tail on the hamster.
这是免费得的.
I got it for free with the purchase of 20 party hats.
麦琪:杰森,这是希腊语.是说生日快乐吗?
Maggie: Jason, this is Greek.Does it say happy birthday?
杰森:哦,买东西的也不庆贺出.不是这个就是"杜卡基斯在88年".
Jason: Well the salesman wasn't sure.It's either that or Dukakis in 88.
麦琪:哦,亲爱的,抱歉我要说你就爱便宜货.
Maggie: Oh honey I'm sorry to insinuate that you were cheap.
杰森:没关系,接受你的抱歉.
Jason: All right apology accepted.No where's Ben?
哦,本呢?他说要帮我找以前剩下的蜡烛的.
He was supposed to help me find last years candles.
麦琪:哦,他和德怀特去买冰激凌了.
Maggie: Oh he and Dwight went to get more ice cream.
杰森:德怀特又来了?
Jason: Dwight 's here again?
麦琪:哦,亲爱的的,他思念开萝尔,他和孤独.
Maggie: Well honey he misses Carol and he's lonely.
杰森:是的,不过,好像这两天我转身就会发现德怀特.
Jason: Yeah but it seems the last couple of days every time I turn around I there's Dwight.
麦琪:杰森,你太夸张了.
Maggie: Jason, you are exaggerating.
杰森:昨天晚上,我在洗手间看报纸,
Jason: Last night he was reading the newspaper over my shoulder,
他就在我的背后看.
in the bathroom.
麦琪:别管他了…另外,他和本相处地很不错.
Maggie: Leave him alone...besides he and Ben are really starting to get along.
德怀特:草坪上的躺椅象征着人类无法解决的难题--人的存在.
Dwight: So you see the lawn chair symbolizes the anthropological conundrum
that is this very existence.
本:太棒了,德怀特,我自己就永远说不出这样的话.不过,该把开萝尔叫回来了.
Ben: That's great Dwight.I never thought I'd hear my self say these words, but
get Carol back now
德怀特:西沃医生,如果你不介意的话,
Dwight: Dr.Seaver I got lickerish pineapple crunch ice cream if that's
我买了凤梨味道的冰激凌.
not too much of a cliché.
杰森:哦,也许我们可以在上面加一点特别的东西.
Jason: Well maybe we can find something exotic to put on top.
德怀特:哦,我早想到了.就加奶油爆米花.
Dwight: Oh, I'm way ahead of you.Creamed corn!!!
迈克:卢克,下来.其他人也都快过来.
Mike: Luke get down here.Everybody else, come here, quick.
德怀特:哇,你买了奶油爆米花,你准备好晚会了.
Dwight: Whoa, you got cream corn, you got a party.
迈克:卢克,你准备好接受生日礼物了吗?
Mike: Luke, you ready for your birthday present?
克莉丝:妈妈,爸爸,巴尼教我怎么耍扑克了.
Chrissy: Mommy, daddy, Barney showed me how to do a card trick.
麦琪:哦,太好了,宝贝…表演一下.
Maggie: Oh great, sweetie...let's see.
Chrissy: Find the queen, where's she hiding?feeling lucky today, buddy
巴尼:好了,孩子,也许我们待会再玩吧…
Barney: Come on kid, maybe we should talk to them a little later...
亚伯:不,快点,巴尼.给大家露一手.
Abe: No come on Barney, show them how you do it.
巴尼:不…
Barney: Nooo...
克莉丝:他比我可强多了.
Chrissy: He's a lot better than I am.
巴尼:哦,好吧.找到Q,它躲到哪里了?
Barney: Well, ok.Find the queen, where's she hiding?
伦敦塔,白金汉宫,汽车旅馆?
Tower eleven, Buckingham palace, motel 6?
本:恕我冒犯,巴尼,
Ben: No offense Barney but you got to get up pretty early in the morning
想骗本西沃,你早上起的还要再早点…你是怎么做到的?
to fool Ben Seav.....How did you do that?
巴尼:哦,我会告诉你的…这比你上次生日可强多了,是不是,亚伯?
Barney: Well, ill tell ya...this is a lot better than your last birthday uh Abe?
麦琪:上次怎么了?
Maggie: Why what happened?
亚伯:哦,关门后,
Abe: Oh, Barney and some of the guys snuck me into the zoo after-hours.
巴尼和几个人把我偷偷带进动物园.哦,我们那天吃的多好啊!
Boy, did we eat well that night!
杰森:你们吃什么了?
Jason: What did you eat?
亚伯:热狗,垃圾箱里全是热狗.
Abe: Hot dogs.The dumpster was full of them.
不管怎么样,
No matter what, you always helped us out.
你总有办法.他总能找到睡的地方和吃的东西.
He can always get us a place to sleep and some food.
巴尼:给你的礼物.
Barney: It's a gift.
杰森:看起来,卢克有你照顾真是幸运.
Jason: It sounds like Luke was pretty lucky to have you looking out for him.
巴尼:是的,哦…请你们原谅,
Barney: Yeah, well...you are gonna have to excuse me;
我要去方便一下.
I have to answer natures call.
妈妈:哦,巴尼,你上楼去吧,在右边的第二个门.
Mom: Oh, Barney, why don't you go upstairs, second door on the right.
巴尼:我老是这样.
Barney: Force of habit.
迈克:各位,我们玩游戏吧,好不好?
Mike: So everybody, what do you say we play some games?
每个人:好啊.
Everybody: Yeah all right.
德怀特:哦,我有个好主意.
Dwight: Oh I have a great one.
本:什么?"骗傻瓜"吗?
Ben: What?Spin the duffus?
德怀特:不是.名字叫听字猜意.
Dwight: Maybe later.This is called semantics.
一个人说一个字,然后大家猜到底是什么意思.
Someone names a word, and then we all try to give it subtle shades of meaning.
杰森:这是女士游戏.开萝尔先认识他的.
Jason: Stay back ladies.Carol saw him first.
听起来,这是在晚会结束的时候才玩的游戏.
That' sounds like the kind of game that usually ends a party.
德怀特:我意识到了.
Dwight: I've noticed that.
杰森:也许,我们可以做做那个叫"抓老鼠尾巴"的游戏,
Jason: Maybe we can build up to that,
怎么样?
but now how about a rousing game of pin the tail on the hamster.
麦琪:照相机呢?我来拍张照片.
Maggie: Where's the camera?I want to get a picture of this.
杰森:在楼上呢,我们柜子里.
Jason: Upstairs, our closet.
亚伯:我去拿.
Abe: Oh I'll get it.
德怀特:呃,关于抓老鼠,
Dwight: Uhm, I just have one question about this hamster thing.
我还有一个问题.怎么才能抓住小老鼠?
How do we hold the little guy down?
亚伯:你干什么了?
Abe: What were you doing?
巴尼:呃,看看其他人是怎么生活的.
Barney: Uh, just seeing how the other half lives.
这些塑像使整个房间很协调,
You know this statue thing pulls this whole room together?
亚伯:你刚才翻西沃太太的首饰盒干什么?巴尼,
Abe: What were you doing in Mrs.Seaver's jewelry box?
你是不是想拿东西?
Barney we're you going to take something?
巴尼:亚伯,你怎么能说出这种话呢?
Barney: Abe, how could you say something like that?
我只是想上厕所,看到这道门开着.
I was on my way to the bathroom and the door was opened.
我知道不应该进来.但是…
I know I shouldn't have come in here but....
我看到了梳妆台上的这个首饰盒.
I saw the jewelry box on the dresser.
以前我就爱看我妈的首饰盒.
I used to look through my moms all the time.
她盒子里有一个小芭蕾舞演员.
Hers had this little dancing ballerina in it.
我只是想看看她这里是否也有.
And I just wanted to see if this one had one too.
亚伯:巴尼,对不起.是的,
Abe: Barney I'm sorry.
你知道我不该冒失地做出这样的结论.嘿,你能原谅我吗?
Yeah, you know I shouldn't have jumped to a conclusion like
that.Hey, you forgive me
巴尼:是的,当然了…算了,
Barney: Yeah sure...come on let's go back down stairs.
我们下楼去吧.对了,你怎么戴这样的帽子.
By the way, what's with the Dukakis hats?
迈克:是有点热,真的很热.
Mike: You're warm.Really really warm.
麦琪:德怀特,德怀特…
Maggie: Dwight, Dwight...
德怀特:在这里,西沃太太…
Dwight: In here Mrs.Seaver...
麦琪:不,不,不.
Maggie: No no no.
德怀特:我不能走,我真赢着呢.
Dwight: I can't leave now, I'm winning.
迈克:卢克,你觉得现在打开礼物怎么样?
Mike: Luke what do you say we open up the presents huh?
德怀特:这是我和开萝尔送的.
Dwight: This one is from me and Carol.
亚伯:叔本华全集.
Abe: The complete works of Schopenhauer.
德怀特:我知道…你读过了.
Dwight: I knew it...you already read it.
亚伯:还没读德语原版呢.
Abe: Even not in its original German.
本:好的,这是我的.
Ben: All right, now mine.
亚伯:瑞格艾伦,锤子和镰刀,护士小组.
Abe: Mega slime, hammer and sickle, the nurses?
本:是的,包括他们的主打单曲-.
Ben: Yeah, it's got their hit single, "turn your head and cough"
亚伯:我能借你的随身听吗?
Abe: Can I borrow your walkman sometime?
本:当然了.
Ben: Sure.
亚伯:好的.
Abe: All right.
杰森:嘿,你该打开我们的了.
Jason: Hey, you wanna open ours next.
亚伯:嘿,给我的随身听…谢谢.
Abe: Hey my own walkman...thanks.
杰森:生日快乐.
Jason: Happy birthday.
麦琪:是的.
Maggie: Uh.
杰森:嘿,这是在结婚纪念日我送你的珍珠吗?
Jason: Hey are those the pearls I gave you for our anniversary?
妈妈:不,亲爱的,
Mom: No honey they are the real ones.
这是真的.有人弄坏了,又用胶水给粘起来了.
Someone broke them and glued them back together with rubber cement.
克莉丝:哦,下面打开我的.
Chrissy: Uh, open mine next.
麦琪:我待会回来.
Maggie: I'll be right back.
克莉丝:这是我们全家…给你的.
Chrissy: It's the whole family...that's you.
亚伯:谢谢.这是我收到的最珍贵的礼物.
Abe: thanks, this is the best present I have ever gotten.
克莉丝:你会贴到你的墙上吗?
Chrissy: will you put it on your wall?
亚伯:我这就去,还要把克里斯蒂娜的海报给撕下来.
Abe: I'll do it right now, ill even move my Christina apple gate poster.
克莉丝:我是在冰箱那里画好的,终于派上用场了.
Chrissy: I made it off the refrigerator.Finally the big time.
亚伯:怎么了,西沃太太?
Abe: Is something wrong Mrs.Seaver?
妈妈:噢,没什么,
Mom: Oh no Luke, I'm just looking for an old ring my grandmother gave me,
卢克.我在找奶奶给我的一枚旧戒指.通常它就放在这里.
its usually right in here.
盒子开着,戒指不见了;克莉丝肯定又拿我的首饰玩了.卢克,巴尼没来过,是不是?
The box was open; Chrissy must have been playing with my jewelry again.Luke, Barney wasn't in here at all was he?
亚伯:巴尼?
Abe: Barney?
麦琪:哦,我的天啊.我都说了什么可怕的话啊,对不起.我的意思是不能因为他没有家,就认为他偷东西.
Maggie: Oh my god, what a horrible thing to say, I'm sorry.I mean I know just because he's homeless doesn't mean he would steal
亚伯:这没什么,西沃太太.
Abe: That's ok Mrs.Seaver.
妈妈:我不能这样,很抱歉.其实开萝尔很喜欢那个戒指.肯定是她借去带到英国去了.我有多傻啊.
Mom: No it isn't and I'm very sorry.I mean Carol loves that ring.I bet she borrowed it to take it to England, how silly of me.Come on birthday boy.Let's go back down stairs.
来吧,小寿星,我们下楼去吧,
Abe: I'll be down in just a second, I'm just gonna hang this up.
亚伯:我一会儿就下楼.我想把它挂起来.
Mom: Ok.
妈妈:好的.
Mike: You got three words, third word is....uuuhh...sounds like....Big!
迈克:三个字,第三个字是…呃…听起来好像…大!
Ben: Hugh!
本:长!
Chrissy: Hair.
克莉丝:头发.
Dwight: Big huge hair, a dolly parton movie.
德怀特:,一部儿童电影.
Ben: If it was a dolly parton movie it be big huge...
本:如果是儿童电影的话,那就是
Jason: Ben!
杰森:本!
Ben: Ok, ok, sounds like hair....
本:好,好,听起来像头发…
Dwight: Oh hair stair, old contrair, smoking hair....Sunny in chair!!!!
德怀特:哦,头发楼梯,大傻瓜,冒烟的头发…晴朗的椅子!!!
Chrissy: Time!
克莉丝:时间到!
Jason: Already?It was truth or dare.And you wait until it's your turn Dwight.
杰森:这么快?是真理或勇敢.还没到你呢,德怀特.
Ben: All right, my turn.
本:好的,该我了.
Mike: Planet of the apes.Sorry, just popped out.
迈克:类人猿星球.对不起,我顺口说的.
Jason: Moving...
杰森:继续…
Mike: You are stealing, you are a robber...
迈克:你在偷东西,你是强盗…
Jason: A layer.
杰森:下蛋鸡.
Abe: Thief.To catch a thief.
亚伯:小偷.抓小偷.
Everybody: All right!
每个人:对.
Abe: Hey Barney it's getting a little chilly in here, want to help me go start a fire?
亚伯:嘿,巴尼,这里有点冷,能帮我把火点起来吗?
Barney: Sure, where do you keep the trash can?
巴尼:好的.你把木柴放哪里了?
Chrissy: My turn.
克莉丝:该我了.本和迈克:不,不.
Ben and Mike: No no.
妈妈:好了,克莉丝也有份这才公平.
Mom: No, come on, it's only fair that Chrissy gets her turn.
本:算了吧,她总是猜错.
Ben: Come on she always reads them wrong.
上一次,她花了半个小时才猜出那个词是芥末.
Last time we spent half an hour truing to figure out the sound of mustard.
巴尼:小子,你可以用这些木柴煮许多土豆…
Barney: Boy, you could cook a lot of potatoes with that...
亚伯:把你从西沃太太首饰盒里拿的戒指交给我.
Abe: I want the ring you took out of Mrs.Seaver's jewelry box.
巴尼:不再那样了.我告诉年我只是看看的.
Barney: Not that again, I told you I was just looking around.
亚伯:把戒指给我.
Abe: I want the ring.
巴尼:不.
Barney: No.
亚伯:我不相信.你怎么还偷别人家的东西呢?
Abe: I don't believe this, how could you just steal something like that?
巴尼:哦,我染上了毒瘾,我需要钱买吸的东西.
Barney: Well, it's to feed my addiction.I'm going through a food withdrawal.
亚伯:但是,你怎么能这样对待收留我,
Abe: But how could you do it to the people who were nice enough to take
爱护我的人呢?嘿,你不需要那个戒指;你玩"三张牌"能挣钱.
me in?Hey you don't need that ring; you do fine playing 3 card Monty.
巴尼:嘿,得了吧.
Barney: Hey come on, there probably wondering where we are...
他们一定在想我们去哪儿了…这会功夫能砍一棵树.我们走.
we could have chopped the whole tree down by now, let's go.
亚伯:别逼我叫警察.
Abe: Don't make me call the cops.
巴尼:我不会相信的.
Barney: I don't believe you.
你穿着考究的衣服站在我面前.
You stand there in those designer clothes,
现在你告诉偷东西是错误的?
and now you tell me it's wrong to steal?
你认为你18岁以后会怎么样?他们有四个孩子.幻想着他们能给你车?
What do you think is going to happen to you when you turn 18?They got four kids.Think they are going to get you a car?
指望送你上大学?
Think that they are going to send you to college?
两年以后你会重新流落街头.
Two years from now, you are going to be back out on the street.
你不属于他们;你属于我们,
Your not one of them, you're one of us.
你清楚,我也清楚,
You know it, and I know it.
所以我说你不会叫警察,对吗?
And that's why your not going to call the cops, are you?
亚伯:是的.
Abe: No.
巴尼:亚伯,好了,我不想看到你这样.我有个办法解决这个问题.我们玩"三张牌"的游戏决定戒指的归属.
Barney: Abe, come on, I don't like to see you like this.I'll tell you
what were going to do.We will play 3 card Monty for the ring
或许你能公平的赢回戒指,
And maybe you can win it back from me fair and square.
亚伯:这怎么是公平呢?总是你赢.
Abe: What's fair about that?You always win.
巴尼:我照顾你,给你三次机会.
Barney: I'll up the odds.I'll give you three tries.
你只要猜对Q,戒指归你.
Find the queen just once, you get the ring.
亚伯:如果我同意呢?
Abe: And if I don't?
巴尼:不然,我就可以一个月都不用担心吃饭了.
Barney: I get to eat regular for a few months.
亚伯:不,我不能用西沃太太的戒指跟你打赌.
Abe: No, I can't gamble with you for Mrs.Seaver's ring.
每个人:哦,大鼻子…大鼻子,芭芭拉…
Everybody: Uh, big nose...big nose, bob hope, Barbara Streisand...
迈克:匹诺曹.对了,我猜着了.
Mike: Pinocchio.Yeah, I got it.
杰森:等等,这里是说危险的联络.
Jason: Wait a minute, this says dangerous liaison.
克莉丝:我更喜欢匹诺曹.
Chrissy: I like Pinocchio better.
巴尼:好了,伙计们,我不该吃了就走.不过,我要回去了.
Barney: Well folks, I hate to eat and run but I got to get back into town.
亚伯:嘿,巴尼,我想我们来玩"三张牌"游戏吧.
Abe: Hey Barney, I thought we were going to play a little three card Monty.
巴尼:你真想玩?
Barney: You wanna play?
亚伯:我说了.
Abe: I said so.
巴尼:好,那好吧.
Barney: Well, all right.
麦琪:哦,好.
Maggie: Oh good.
本:哦,别生气,卢克.我押巴尼赢.
Ben: Oh no offense, but my money is on Barney.
杰森:我也是.
Jason: Me too.
巴尼:好吧,从前有个睡美人,
Barney: Ok, once upon a time there was a sleeping beauty,
英俊的王子必须打开一扇正确的门,才能用吻来唤醒她.噢,
and a handsome prince had to open the right door, to wake her with a kiss.
抱歉,不是这扇.
Sorry, wrong door.
Find the queen, where's she hiding, upstairs downstairs, in my lady's chamber
还是在夫人的房间里?运气不好,孩子.再来.
Tough luck kid, try again.
迈克:放弃吧,卢克.你自己说过,没人能赢他.
Mike: Face it Luke, you said it yourself, nobody can beat this guy.
亚伯:我选这张,因为如果这张是2,
Abe: I choose this one, because if this is the two, and this is the seven,
这张是,那这张一定是Q.
then this must be the queen.
每个人:嘿,对啊,对.
Everybody: Hey, all right, yeah.
麦琪:如果大家玩完了游戏,到厨房去.每个人都去,卢克留下.
Maggie: So if everybody is finished playing games, in the kitchen.Everyone except Luke
杰森:我去拿叉子.
Jason: I'll get the forks.
迈克和本:好.
Mike and Ben: Right.
德怀特:我去拿盘子和奶油爆米花.
Dwight: I'll get the plates and the cream corn.
巴尼:你一直都知道吗?
Barney: You knew the whole time?
亚伯:实际上,我真的以为你是个世界上唯一诚实的"三张牌"玩家.
Abe: Actually I really thought you were the worlds only honest three card Monty player
巴尼:好,给你戒指.嘿,听着,
Barney: Yep, here's your ring.Hey look, kid it's part of life on the street.
孩子,这就是流浪街头的结果.有时候,为了活下去,你不得不把诚实放到一边.
See there comes a time when you have to put your priorities at work.
亚伯:但这仍然改变了你做了错事这个事实.嘿,
Abe: That still doesn't change the fact that this kind of stuff is wrong.
你为什么不去找份工作.你知道?重新开始.
Hey, why don't you get a job, you know?Start over.
巴尼:说起来容易.我这副尊容,
Barney: That's easy for you to say,
招工部门连看都不看我一眼.
I don't exactly have the look the employment agencies want.
亚伯:给你.
Abe: Here.
巴尼:这是干什么?
Barney: What's this for?
亚伯:留个纪念.
Abe: Something to remember me by.
巴尼:哦,这会让那些家伙们开心的.你不介意我…
Barney: Hmm, this should impress the guys.Mind if I...
亚伯:去当了吧.
Abe: Go ahead and pawn it.
换来的钱可以让你几个星期不愁吃饭.嘿,
It should get you a few weeks downtown and some food.
还能买几件衣服面试的时候用.
Hey, and some clothes for job interviews.
巴尼:谢谢你,亚伯.多保重,生日快乐.
Barney: Thanks Abe.Take care of yourself, happy birthday.
每个人:祝你生日快乐,祝你生日快乐,
Everybody: Happy birthday to you, happy birthday dear Luke,
亲爱的卢克,祝你生日快乐.
happy birthday to you.
杰森:巴尼走了?
Jason: Did Barney leave already?
亚伯:是的,他走了.
Abe: Yeah he just left.
麦琪:过来,小寿星,吹蜡烛吧.
Maggie: Well come on birthday boy, blow out your candles.
亚伯:哦,不,谢谢.我一点都不饿.
Abe: Oh no thanks, I'm not really that hungry.
杰森:出什么事了?
Jason: Something wrong?
亚伯:没有.
Abe: No.
德怀特:噢,我知道了.
Dwight: Oh, I know what it is.
每次聚会后我都失落,气球开始漏气,
I always get depressed after parties, the balloons start to deflate,
客人们都离去,欢笑都结束了…
the guests all leave, water picks all get put away...
请原谅我眼睛里有东西.
Excuse me; I have something in my eye.
麦琪:噢,行了,
Maggie: Oh come on its not over yet,
还没有结束呢.卢克,有些礼物你还没有打开看呢?
Luke you haven't even finished opening your presents.
亚伯:不,我都看了.
Abe: Yes I have.
杰森:不,还有这个.
Jason: Not this one.
亚伯:哦,这是什么?
Abe: Well, what is it?
杰森:这是一张存折,你上大学用的.
Jason: That's a savings bond, for college.
亚伯:你们大家不必对我这么好.
Abe: You guys don't have to do this for me.
杰森:哦,我们这样做不是因为不得不这样,
Jason: Well we didn't do it because we have to Luke,
卢克,是以为你是这个家庭的一份子.
we did it because you are part of this family.
麦琪:生日快乐.
每个人:生日快乐,卢克.
00:22:31,600
Maggie: Happy birthday. Everybody: Happy birthday Luke.